{
    "subject": "resource/Nia_Long",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Brooklyn,_New_York",
    "human_readable": "Nia Long was born in Brooklyn, New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8928269147872925,
            "question": "Is Nia Long from New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.845160961151123,
            "question": "Where was Nia Long born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7016778588294983,
            "question": "What is the name of the borough Nia Long was born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6934000253677368,
            "question": "In what US state was Nia Long born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.665488064289093,
            "question": "What is the name of the borough where Nia Long was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2157706320285797,
            "question": "Where is Brooklyn located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20724445581436157,
            "question": "Is Brooklyn a part of New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11572284996509552,
            "question": "What is the name of the US state where Brooklyn is located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10099063068628311,
            "question": "Name a city in New York State."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05534559488296509,
            "question": "Can you name another borough in New York City?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nia Long was born in Brooklyn, New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7725_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a city in New York State.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7725_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the US state where Brooklyn is located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7725_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Brooklyn a part of New York City?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7725_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7725_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Nia Long was born in Brooklyn, New York. For instance, from the document at `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7725/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt`, it is mentioned: \"Nia Long is from Brooklyn, New York, where she was born on October 30, 1970.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}